Guide to the James Ferlo Papers, 1963-2015 AIS.1998.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pennsylvania State Senate, 2000-2015; 2004-2013; II.
  - Legislation Issues and Correspondence, 2000-2014; 2004-2010; 3.
    - Alphabetical Subject File, 2000-2014
      - National Guard, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Net Metering, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Newspapers Notices, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Newspapers, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Nicolas's Law, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - No Child Left Behind, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Notary Law Info, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Nuisance Bar Task Force, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Nuisance Bars, 2003-2005 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Nurse Protection, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Nursing Bills, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Nursing Homes, 2006 (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Nursing: Banning Mandatory Overtime, 2005-2008 (Box 73, Folder 18)
      - One Handgun per Month, 2002-2003 (Box 73, Folder 19)
      - Open Records, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 20)
      - Ophtamology, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 21)
      - Organ Donor Life Act, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 22)
      - Ounce of Prevention Act, undated (Box 73, Folder 23)
      - Our Pennsylvania, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 24)
      - PA Archaeological Council, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 25)
      - PA Biolegislative Day, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 26)
      - PA Chamber, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 27)
      - PA Coalition Against Rape, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 28)
      - PA Municipal Authorities Association, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 29)
      - PA School Choice- SB1, 2010-2011 (Box 73, Folder 30)
      - Parole for Violent Offenders, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 31)
      - Patient Safety, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 32)
      - Pay Day Lending, 2012-2013 (Box 73, Folder 33)
      - Pay Increase, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 34)
      - Paycheck Deduction, 2014 (Box 73, Folder 35)
      - Pennsylvania Dietetic Association, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 36)
      - Pennsylvania Gaming Control Board, 2007 (Box 73, Folder 37)
      - Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency Sale, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 38)
      - Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board (PLCB), 2003 (Box 73, Folder 39)
      - Pennsylvania Pharmacists Association, 2011 (Box 73, Folder 40)
      - Pipeline Safety, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 41)
      - Pittsburgh Act 47, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 42)
      - Pittsburgh Public Schools Teacher Evaluation, 2014 (Box 73, Folder 43)
      - Pittsburgh Public Schools, 2012-2013 (Box 73, Folder 44)
      - Pittsburgh: Wilkinsburg Fire Department, 2010 (Box 73, Folder 45)
      - Police Pensions, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 46)
      - Police Residency, 2003-2005 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Police Support, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Port Authority of Allegheny County, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Portfolio Standard, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Predatory Lending, 2000 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Predatory Lending, 2001-2003 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Predatory Lending, 2003-2005 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Prevailing Wage, 2005-2012 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Prison Reform, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Property Tax Reform, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Property Tax Reform, 2005-2006 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Public Notice, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Public Transportation, 2004-2007 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Public Welfare Code- Youth Services, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Purely Public Charities, 2007 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Race to the Top, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 16)
      - RAD, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 17)
      - Regulatory Review, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Residential Construction Dispute Resolution Act, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Right to Know Law, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - SB 81, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Separations Act, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 2003-2005 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Sexual Offenders, 2004 (Box 75, Folder 7)
      - Small Games of Chance Act, 2013 (Box 75, Folder 8)
      - Small Games of Chance, 2007-2009 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Smoking Ban, 2005-2008 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Sprinklers, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 11)
      - State Police, 2004-2013 (Box 75, Folder 12)
      - Statewide School Employee Healthcare Benefit Program, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 13)
      - Strongland Chamber of Commerce, 2007-2010 (Box 75, Folder 14)
      - Sunday Beer Sales, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 15)
      - Sunshine Act, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      - Survivor Benefits, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 17)
      - Sustainable Communities, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 18)
      - Swaps (Schools), 2010 (Box 75, Folder 19)
      - T.R.I.D., 2004 (Box 75, Folder 20)
      - Teacher Tuition Reimbursement, 2001-2003 (Box 75, Folder 21)
      - Tobacco Free Program, 2005-2010 (Box 75, Folder 22)
      - Tobacco Settlement Act, 2006-2007 (Box 75, Folder 23)
      - Tobacco Settlement Act, 2006-2007 (Box 75, Folder 24)
      - Tort Reform, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 25)
      - Tow Truck, 2013-2014 (Box 75, Folder 26)
      - Township Commissioners, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 27)
      - UCC, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 28)
      - Unemployment Compensation Rate, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 29)
      - Uniform Construction Code, 2004-2007 (Box 75, Folder 30)
      - Uniform Emergency Volunteer Health Practitioners Act, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 31)
      - UPMC vs. Highmark, 2009-2014 (Box 75, Folder 32)
      - Vehicle Emissions, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 33)
      - Verified Voting, 2013 (Box 75, Folder 34)
      - Verizon, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 35)
      - Veterans Issues, 2003-2008 (Box 75, Folder 36)
      - Video Poker, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 37)
      - Visitability, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 38)
      - Voice over IP, 2007 (Box 75, Folder 39)
      - Volunteer Fire Fighters, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 40)
      - Volunteer's Tuition Reimbursement, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 41)
      - Volunteers, 2004 (Box 75, Folder 42)
      - Voter IDs, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 43)
      - Voter Verified Papers Ballots, 2005-2006 (Box 75, Folder 44)
      - Waivers and School Code, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 45)
      - Water Quality, 2012 (Box 75, Folder 46)
      - Wine Legislation, 2005-2006 (Box 75, Folder 47)
      - Workers Compensation, 2004-2005 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 30/ Broadband Network, 2002-2008
      - Cable Deregulation, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Chapter 30, 2002-2004 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Chapter 30, 2003-2005 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Chapter 30, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Gaming, 2003-2011
      - Gaming Addiction, 2011 (Box 76, Folder 6)
      - Gaming Control Board of PA, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 7)
      - Gaming Control Board, 2006-2008 (Box 76, Folder 8)
      - Gaming Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 9)
      - Gaming Licensing, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 10)
      - Gaming Standardbreed Breeders Association of PA, 2003-2004 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Healthcare, 2003-2012
      - Governor's Office of Health Care Reform, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Health Care Legislation, 2003-2007 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Health Care Legislation, 2003-2007 (Box 76, Folder 14)
      - Health Savings Accounts, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 15)
      - Healthcare (Single Payer) 1, 2008-2009 (Box 76, Folder 16)
      - Healthcare (Single Payer) 1, 2008-2009 (Box 76, Folder 17)
      - Healthcare Costs, 2004-2007 (Box 76, Folder 18)
      - Healthcare Costs, 2004-2007 (Box 76, Folder 19)
      - Healthcare Costs, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 20)
      - Healthcare Facilities Act, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 21)
      - Healthcare Single Payer Healthcare, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 22)
      - Healthcare Stakeholders 2, 2003-2011 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Healthcare Stakeholders 2, 2003-2011 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Healthcare Stakeholders 2, 2003-2011 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Healthcare, 2005-2008 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Healthcare, 2011-2012 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - MCARE vs. Prescription for PA, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Medicaid Estate Recovery, 2010 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Medicaid, 2012-2014 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Prescription Benefit Managers, 2008-2012 (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Prescription Contraception Equity, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Prescription Drugs, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Prescription Equity, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Prescription for PA, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Single Payer Presentation, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Marcellus Shale/Natural Gas, 2010-2012
      - Marcellus Shale 1, 2010 (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Marcellus Shale 2, 2010-2011 (Box 77, Folder 16-17)
      - Marcellus Shale 3, 2010-2011 (Box 77, Folder 18-19)
      - Natural Gas (Marcellus Shale) Drilling Oversight, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Natural Gas Legislation, 2011-2012 (Box 77, Folder 21-28)
      - Natural Gas Legislation, 2011-2012 (Box 78, Folder 1-4)
    - Municipal Pension Reform, 2008-2010
      - Municipal Pension Reform, 2008-2010 (Box 78, Folder 5-13)
    - Public School Employees (PSERS) and State Employees Retirement Systems (SERS), 2005-2012
      - Public School Employees (PSERS) and State Employees Retirement Systems (SERS), 2005-2012 (Box 78, Folder 14-16)
      - Public School Employees (PSERS) and State Employees Retirement Systems (SERS), 2005-2012 (Box 79, Folder 1-9)
      - State Employee's Retirement, 2004-2009 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Public Utilities/Electricity, 2002-2010
      - Allegheny Power, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Alternate Fuels Heritage, 2007 (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Economic Impact of Renewable Energy in PA, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Electricity, 2009-2010 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Energy Policy Special Session, 2006-2007 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Energy Policy, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - Energy Rate Legislation, 2005-2008 (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Energy Rate Legislation, 2005-2008 (Box 80, Folder 1-11)
      - PA Public Utility Commission, 2007-2009 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - PJM Interconnection, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - PPL Electric Utilities, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Public Utilities/Electricity- CMU Publications, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Public Utility Rates and Legislation, 2008-2010 (Box 80, Folder 16-17)
      - Public Utility Rates and Legislation, 2008-2010 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - Public Utility Rates and Legislation, 2008-2010 (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
      - UGI Utilities, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Job Recommendations and Requests, 2003-2009; 2004-2008; 4.
    The Job Recommendations and Requests subseries contains materials regarding colleagues and acquaintances of Ferlo during his time as a Pennsylvania Senator, arranged alphabetically by last name or topic.
    - Abdulovic, Mary Kay, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Act 33 Clearances, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny County Court of Common Pleas Joe Williams Nomination, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Baldwin, Cynthia, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Baylor, John, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Bob O'Connor Administration, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Cabinet Bios and Info, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Court of Common Pleas, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Delta Foundation, undated (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Executive Nominations, 2004-2008 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Hall, Julia, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Job Requests (Resumes, Jobs), 2006-2008 (Box 81, Folder 16-17)
    - Jobs, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - Kemp, Janice, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Kovacik, Albert, 2007-2008 (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - Kramer, Joseph Department Orientation and Info., 2009 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Kuzmanko, Keith, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - Letter of Recommendation Info, 2003 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Lynch, Bernie, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Martinez, Gil, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Martino, Len, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Miller, Robert, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Moshier, Gary, undated (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Muhammed, Akhi Raheem, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Nomination Requests, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 30)
    - Rua, Lisa, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 31)
    - Snyder, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 32)
    - Watson, Wrenna, 2005-2006 (Box 81, Folder 33)
    - West, Lauri Ann, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 34)
    - Will, Shawn, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 35)
    - Williams, Joseph, 2008 (Box 81, Folder 36)
    - Woodruff, Dwayne, 2005 (Box 81, Folder 37)
    - Wright, Lloyd, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - State Finances, 2001-2015; 2005-2011; 5.
    The State Finances subseries contains materials related to Pennsylvania state budgetary issues and tax issues, as well as funding correspondence related to those budget and tax legislative decisions. Topics include the Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh (URA), Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ), Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) and Project 15206.
    - Budgetary Issues, 2001-2014
      - Accountability Block Grant, 2004-2008 (Box 81, Folder 39)
      - After School Programs, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 40)
      - Arena (A New One), 2001-2007 (Box 81, Folder 41)
      - Armstrong County, 2011 (Box 81, Folder 42)
      - Bidwell Training, ca 2010 (Box 81, Folder 43)
      - Black Fly Program, 2005-2008 (Box 81, Folder 44)
      - Budget Address, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 45)
      - Budget Requests, 2005-2006 (Box 81, Folder 46)
      - Budget, 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 47)
      - Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 81, Folder 48)
      - Budget, 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Budget, 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Budget, 2009-2010 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Cancer Center (University of Pittsburgh), 2003 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Capital Budget Updates, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Capital Budget, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 7-8)
      - Capital Budget, 2010 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Carnegie Science Center Traffic, 2007 (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - Childrens' Hospital of Pittsburgh, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Crossing Guards/City of Pittsburgh School District, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Debt Service, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Disabilities Budget, 2010 (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - Farm Bureau, 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - Fiscal Office, 2009-2010 (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Food, 2009-2012 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - Funding Formula, 2011-2013 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - General Fund, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Health Insurance, 2006-2010 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - Heinz History Center, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Letters from Constituents, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - Liquor Control Board, 2011-2012 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Mass Transit Budget, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - McGowan Budget, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - Newspaper Articles re: Budget, 2003 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Pension Plans (Local Government), 2004 (Box 82, Folder 27)
      - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - Pittsburgh School District, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 29)
      - Public Employees Retirement Commission, 2012 (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - Redevelopment Capital Assistance Program (RACP), 2012 (Box 82, Folder 31)
      - Renewable Energy, 2011 (Box 82, Folder 32)
      - Transportation Issues, 2007-2009 (Box 82, Folder 33)
      - Treasury, 2010 (Box 82, Folder 34)
      - Tuition Relief Program, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 35)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 2012 (Box 82, Folder 36)
      - Urban Redevelopment Authority (URA), 2006-2009 (Box 82, Folder 37)
      - Urban Redevelopment Authority (URA), 2006-2009 (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
      - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, 2007-2011 (Box 83, Folder 3-8)
      - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, 2014 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Wilkinsburg, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Women and Girls Foundation, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Funding Correspondence, 2001-2015
      - 911 Center Funding, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - Abandoned Mine Relocation Fund, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - Access to Work, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - ACORN, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Act 47 (Municipalities Financial Recovery Program), 2007-2009 (Box 83, Folder 16-21)
      - Adult Basic and Literary Education, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 22)
      - African-American Cultural Center, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 23)
      - Agricultural Conservation Easements, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 24)
      - AIDS, 2006 (Box 83, Folder 25)
      - Alcosan, undated (Box 83, Folder 26)
      - ALS, 2010 (Box 83, Folder 27)
      - Allegheny Commons, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 28)
      - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 29)
      - Allegheny County Conservation District, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 30)
      - Allegheny County Housing Authority (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Allegheny County Law Enforcement Grant, 2005-2008 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Allegheny County Requests, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Allegheny County, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ), 2005-2006 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ), 2010 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Blawnox Signage, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 7)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Board Agendas, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 8)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Bridge Street, 2011-2012 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Housing, 2013 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Partner Meeting, 2013 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Personnel (Box 84, Folder 12)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Transition, 2012-2014 (Box 84, Folder 13)
      - Allegheny River Towns Enterprise Zone (ARTEZ): Transition Presentation, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 14)
      - Allegheny Township, 2003-2007 (Box 84, Folder 15)
      - Allegheny Valley Commuter Railroad, 2003-2004 (Box 84, Folder 16)
      - Alma-Ilery Medical Center, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 17)
      - Apollo Borough, 2003-2005 (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - Approved Private Schools, 2013 (Box 84, Folder 19)
      - Area Agency on Aging, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 20)
      - Armstrong County Health Services, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 21)
      - Armstrong County Human Services, 2006-2007 (Box 84, Folder 22)
      - Armstrong County, 2005-2011 (Box 84, Folder 23)
      - Arsenal Family and Children's Center, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 24)
      - Arsenal Family and Children's Center, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 25)
      - Arthritis Foundation, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 26)
      - Arts, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 27)
      - Aspinwall Marina, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 28)
      - Asset, Inc., 2005 (Box 84, Folder 29)
      - Autism, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 30)
      - AWK Development Inc., 2002 (Box 84, Folder 31)
      - Middle Street, 2013 (Box 84, Folder 32)
      - Ben Franklins, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 33)
      - Big Brother Big Sister, 2006-2007 (Box 84, Folder 34)
      - Blawnox Borough, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 35)
      - Bloomfield Development Corporation (BDC) Pedestrian Study, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 36)
      - Bloomfield Parking Lot, 2013 (Box 84, Folder 37)
      - Bryant Street 5806-5808 Grants, 2008-2010 (Box 84, Folder 38)
      - Budget Requests, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 39)
      - Budget-Education, 2003-2008 (Box 84, Folder 40)
      - Buffalo Township Municipal Authority, 2008 (Box 84, Folder 41)
      - Burtner House, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 42)
      - Carlow University, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 43)
      - Carnegie Library, 2005-2010 (Box 84, Folder 44)
      - Carnegie Library, 2005-2008 (Box 84, Folder 45)
      - Carnegie Mellon University, 2007 (Box 84, Folder 46)
      - Carnegie Museum, undated (Box 84, Folder 47)
      - Catholic Youth Association, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 48)
      - CCAC, 2003-2009 (Box 84, Folder 49)
      - CDBG Funding, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 50)
      - Center For Independent Living, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 51)
      - Child Care, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 52)
      - Children's Home of Pittsburgh, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 53)
      - Children's Museum, 2003-2007 (Box 84, Folder 54)
      - Childrens' Museum, 2006-2007 (Box 84, Folder 55)
      - City County, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 56)
      - Clean Energy Programs, 2003-2009 (Box 84, Folder 57-58)
      - Clean Green Laundry Co-Op, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 59)
      - Commonwealth Financing Agency, 2005-2006 (Box 84, Folder 60)
      - Commonwealth Universal Research Enhancement, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 61)
      - Community Based Care, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 62)
      - Community Colleges, 2004-2005 (Box 84, Folder 63)
      - Community Colleges, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 64)
      - Community Food Bank, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 65)
      - Community Infrastructure and Tourism Fund (CITF), 2005-2007 (Box 84, Folder 66)
      - Conservation Districts, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 67)
      - Consumer Workforce Council, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 68)
      - Corrections, 2006-2009 (Box 84, Folder 69)
      - Council on the Arts, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 70)
      - Cribs for Kids, ca 2009 (Box 84, Folder 71)
      - Crime Prevention Association of Western PA, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 72)
      - Croatian- American Cultural and Economic Alliance, undated (Box 84, Folder 73)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) "CR", March 2007 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Embedded, 2007-2008 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Embedded, 2009 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants Round II, December 2006 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants, September 2007 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants, December 2007 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants, 2009-2010 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants, 2010-2011 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants Round I, September 2008 (Box 85, Folder 9-10)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grants Applications, February 2004 (Box 85, Folder 11-12)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, September 2004 (Box 85, Folder 13-14)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, December 2004 (Box 85, Folder 15-16)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, September 2005 (Box 85, Folder 17-18)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications Round II, December 2005 (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, March 2006 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications Round III, March 2006 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, September 2006 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications Round I, September 2006 (Box 86, Folder 6-7)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, December 2006 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, March 2007 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, September 2007 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, December 2007 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - Department of Community and Economic Development (DCED) Grant Applications, 2008 (Box 86, Folder 12)